Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Original Moffit Working Scores
  - “Dream” (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - “Drum Cadence” (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - “Duel Conductor”; B Band (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - “Ear Poppin’ Fanfare No. 1” (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - “East Fairmont Alma Mater” (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - “Eaton Ohio Fight Song” (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - “EBB Tide” (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - “Eli’s Comin’” (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - “Elvis Greatest Hits” (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - “En Kelohenv” (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - “The Entertainer” (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - “Entry Fanfare II” (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - “Enys Gnal Dlua”; “Auld Lang Syne” (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - “Enys Gnal Dlua” (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - “Espana Cani” (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - "Everything’s Comin’ Up Roses”, September 1960 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - “Evil Ways” (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - “E.W.C. Alma Mater”; Edward Waters College (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - “E.W.C. Fight Song” (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - “Eyes of Texas” (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - “Ezekiel” (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - “Factory Music” (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - “Falcon Fight Song”, August 18, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - “Falcon’s Victory March” (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - “Fanfares No. 1 and No. 2” (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - “Fanfare No. 4” (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - “Fanfare No. 6” (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - “Fanfare No. 7” (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - “Fanfare Trumpets” (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - “Fanfare for Rocky” (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - “Fanfare for Rocky II” (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - “1812 Fantabulous I” (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - “1812 Fantabulous II” (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - “1812 Fantabulous II” (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - “1812 Fantabulous IV” (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - “1812 Fantabulous V” (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - “1812 Fantabulous VI” (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - “Fever” (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - “Feelin’ Groovy” (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - “Feeling Stronger” (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - “A Fifth of Beethoven” (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - “Fight On” (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - “Fight On J.U.” (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - “Fight Song Intros”; UH (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - “Fight On”; Penn. (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - “Fight Song Fanfare No. 3” (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - “Finger Busters” (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - “Five Days From Home” (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - “Five Feet Two” (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - “Flashdance” (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - “Florida A&M” (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - “Florida State Song” (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - “Flying Trapeze” (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - “From This Moment On” (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - “From This Moment On” (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - “For the Honor of Old Purdue” (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - “Forward Falcons – Bowling Green” (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - “Four Leaf Clover” (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - “Free” (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - F.F.A (Songslides) Listings (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - “Games People Play” (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - “Guadeamus Igitur” (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - “Georgia” (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - “Get It On” (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - “Get Ready” (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - “Gillette” (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - “Girl Talk” (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - “Gloria Patri” (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - “Go U Northwestern”, December 17, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - “Go U Northwestern II” (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - “Go U Northwestern” Fanfare (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - “Go J.U.” (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - “God Bless America” (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - “God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen" (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - “Going to Kansas City” (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - “Good Morning Houston” (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - “Goodnight Ladies” (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "No. 3 Goodnight Ladies” (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - “Good Morning America” (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - “Goody Goody”, September 1960 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - “Goody Goody II”, December 1965 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - “Goofus”, December 1965 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - “Gold and Blue”; Crawfordsville, Indiana Alma Mater, June 17, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - “Golden Arm”, October 2, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - “Granda”, September 1962 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - “Grandioso” (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - “Grand Old Flag” (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - “Grazing in the Grass” (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - “Greatest Rock Hits” (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - “Greatest Rock Hits” (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - “Green Berets” (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - “Green Peppers” (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - “Great Gate” (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - “Green Onions” (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - “Grove City College”; “Alma Mater”, August 7, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - “Growing Music” (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - “Gunsmoke”’ (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - “Hail Fanfare” (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - “Hail Loco II” (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - “Hail Loyola”, March 13, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - “Hail Purdue”, January 14, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - “Hail Purdue Fanfare” (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - “Hail Purdue-Verse” (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - “Hail Purdue-Vocal” (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - “Hail State-Mississippi State” (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - “Hail the F.F.A.” (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - “Hail to Georgia” (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - “Hail to Thee” (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - “Hail to Thee”; West Lafayette (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - “Hail to U.N.F.” (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - “Hail Wichita” (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - “Halftime Fanfare No. 2” (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - “Hallmark Theme” (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - “Hall of the Mountain King” (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - “Hark the Herald Angels Sing”, August 19, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - “Harrison Fight” (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - “Haua Nagila”, May 2, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - “Have a Coke and Smile” (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - “Have You Never Been Mellow”, March 2, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - “Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas” (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - “Hawaii” (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - “Hawaiian War Chant”, October 25, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - “Hawaiian War Chant II” (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - “Head Medley”, October 8, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - “Head and Eyes” (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - “Heart”, November 1, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - “Heaven Knows” (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - “Hello Dolly” (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - “Here Comes Santa Claus” (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - “Here Comes the Band”; All (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - “Here Comes the Bride” (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - “Here Comes the Showboat” (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - “Here Comes the King” (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - “Here We Come a Caroling” (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - “Hey Look Me Over” (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - “Hey Look Me Over II” (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - “Hi Name Cheer”; No. 19 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - “Hi John Cheer” (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - “Hillside High School Alma Mater” (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - “Hoist Sweet in F” (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - “Holiday for Strings” (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - “Holiday for T-Bones”, December 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - “Hollywood Fanfare” (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - “Homecoming Ceremony”; p. 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - “Homecoming Ceremony”; p. 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - “Home for the Holidays” (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - “Home Sweet Home”; No. 20 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - “Hooray U.S.A.” (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - “Hoosier Pride”, May 26, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - “The Honeydripper” (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - “Houston” (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - “Houston Fight Song” (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - “Houston (Mother)”, November 1, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - “Houston Oilers” (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - “How Dry I Am” (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - “How High the Moon” (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - “Huskies Fight” (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - “I Ain’t Down Yet”, January 19, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - “I Could Have Danced All Night”, November 14, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - “I Don’t Know How to Love Him” (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - “Idaho” (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - “I Hear the Bells On Christmas” (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - “I Look at Heaven” (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - “I Love a Parade”, February 13, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - “I Love Paris II”, October 1962 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - “I Love You Truly” (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - “Illinois” (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - “Illinois Loyalty Part I” (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - “I’m a Jayhawk”, December 1962 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - “I’m Just Wild About Harry”, November 29, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - “Invocation of Alberich” (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - “Impossible Dream”, October 10, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - “In Heaven There Ain’t No Beer” (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - “In the Mood” (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - “Indiana” (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - “Indian Cheer” (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - “Indiana, Our Indiana”, October 1961 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - “Indianapolis” (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - “Integer Vitae” (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - “Intermission Riff”, December 4, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - “Intermission Riff II”, December 21, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - “Iowa” (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - “Iowa Fight Song”, Summer 1982 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - “Iowa, On to Victory”, February 1961 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - “It Came Upon a Midnight”, August 26, 197 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - “It’s All Right With Me”, September 1961 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - “It’s All Right With Me II”, September 28, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - “It’s Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas” (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - “It’s So Easy”, November 9, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - “I Only Want to Be With You”, October 20, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - “I.U. Fanfare” (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - “I.U. Fanfare – Trumpet” (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - “I Want a Girl” (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - “Jacksonville Blues” (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - “Jaguars” (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - “Jazz Me Blues”, October, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - “Jingle Bells”, September 22, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - “Jingle Bells Chorus” (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - “Jingle Bells-Verse” (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - “John Henry” (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - “John Henry II” (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - “Johnny Comes Marching”, November 3, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - “Johnny One Note”, February 26, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - “Johnny’s Theme”, November 9, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - “Johnson Rag”, September 1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - “Johnson Rag II”, February 17, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - “Jolly Good Fellow” (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - “Jolly Old St. Nicholas” (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - “Joshua”, October 29, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - “Joy”, March 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - “Joy to the World” (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - “J.U. Alma Mater” (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - “J.U. Dolphin Intros” (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - “Just One of Those Things”, September 8, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - “K-K-K-Keady” (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - “Kansas” (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - “Karma Chameleon” (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - “Kentucky” (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - “King of the Road”, October 18, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - “Knock on Wood” (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - “Lamar University” (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - “Lassus T-Bone” (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - “Lassus Trombone”, October 31, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - “Lazy River”, January 9, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - “Leap Frog” (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - “Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow” (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - “Let Me Call You Sweetheart” (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - “Let Me Entertain You” (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - “Life is a Song” (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - “Lightly” (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - “Light My Fire” (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - “Little Boat”, November 16, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - “Live and Let Die”, December 22, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - “Lola” (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - “Lolly Pops and Roses” (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - “Lonely Bull”, February 21, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - “Louisiana” (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - “Louisville”, December 8, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - “Lover”; Acc. Solo (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - “Lover II”, December 1960 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - “Lullaby of Birdland” (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - “Lullaby of Broadway” (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - “Mack the Knife” (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - “Malaguena” (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - “Malaguena II” (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - “Maine” (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - “Mambo Jambo”, January 1962 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - “Mame” (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - “The Man with the Horn” (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - “March” (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - “Marie”, November 1963 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - “Marching Band Warm-Ups” (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - “Maryland” (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - “Master” (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - “Massachusetts” (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - “MacDonald’s”, October 21, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - “Medley” (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - “Medley 67” (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - “Memories” (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - “Memphis State” (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - “Merry-Go-Round”, November 8, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - “Mexican Shuffle”, February 10, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - “Mickey Mouse March” (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - “Milwee Pep Song” (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - “Minnesota” (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - “Minnesota River", October 1961 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous Music Parts (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous Sheet Music (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - “Miss America Intro” (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - “Mississippi” (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - “Mississippi” (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - “Mississippi Mud”, October 1960 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - “Mississippi State University” (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - “Missouri” (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - “Monday, Monday”, March 11, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - “Money, Money, Money” (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - “Montana” (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - “Morehead State University Fight Song” (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - “Mountain Greenery”, September 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - “M.S.U. Pre-Game Fight Song” (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - “The Music Man 76” (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - “Muskrat Ramble”, September 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - “Musical Cheers” (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - “Musical Hints” (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - “Must Be Jelly”, February 12, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - “Macarena” (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - “Major Tony” (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - “Manhattan Skyline” (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - “March America” (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - “Mighty Oregon” (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - “Minerva H.S. Alma Mater” (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - “Minnesota Rouser” (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - “Misty” (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - “Mississippi Mud” (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - “M.M.M. Intros” (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - “Moonlight Serenade I” (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - “Moonlight Serenade II” (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - “Muppets Medley” (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - “Music Americans Sing” (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - “Musical Cheers” (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - “Musical Cocktail” (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - “Music for Marching Percussion” (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - “Music, Music, Music” (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - “Muskrat Ramble” (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - “My Beautiful Lady” (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - “My Life II” (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - “Name of the Game” (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - “National Anthem” (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - “Never Been Kissed” (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - “Newscore-D” (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - “Newsreel” (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - “New Star Spangled Banner”, August 10, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - “Night and Day I” (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - “Night and Day II” (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - “Night and Day Ending” (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - “Night Train” (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - “Nimitz Intros” (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - “Nittany Lion” (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - “North Carolina” (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - “North Dakota” (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - “Not From Dixie” (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - “North Texas Fight Song” (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - “Not Fragile” (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - “Northeast Louisiana University Fight Song” (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - “Notre Dame Victory March” (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - “Notre Dame Victory March” (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - “O Christmas Tree” (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - “Ohio” (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - “Oklahoma” (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - “On the Banks” Fanfare” (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - “On the Radio” (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - “On the Shelf”, January 27, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - “On Wisconsin” (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - “Once in a Lifetime” (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - “One” (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - “One”; (From the Musical “Chorus Line”) (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - “Opus in Pastels I” (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - “Opus in Pastels II” (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - “Oregon” (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - “Original Boogie Woogie” (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - “Osprey Intros” (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - “O Tannenbaum” (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Other Fanfare Scores (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - “Our Boys Will Shine” (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - “Overture 1812”; A Band (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - “Overture 1812”; B Band (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - “Our Director” (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - “Onward Christian Soldier” (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - “On Wisconsin” (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - “Ode to Joy”; (F.C.C.J.) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - “One” (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - “Old Man River”; Brass (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - “Ode to Billy-Joe”; Disco (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - “Old Devil Moon”, October 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - “Old MacDonald” (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - “Old Man River” (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - “Old Man River II”, November 3, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - “Olympic Fanfare”, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - “Olympic Fanfare II” (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Olympic Fanfare Happy Birthday” (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - “On, On Buffaloes” (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - “Operator” (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - “Orb and Scepter” (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - “Oregon State Fight Song” (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - “Oriental Intro” (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - “Our Band” (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - “Overture for Tommy”, November 11, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - “Oye Negra” (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - “Parade of the Toy Soldiers” (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - “Parade of the Wooden Soldiers”, October 31, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - “Patterns of Motion”; Drill Music (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - “Peanut Vendor” (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - “Peanut Vendor II” (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - “Peanut Vendor III” (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - “Pecanoe Centennial March" (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - “Pennsylvania” (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - “Pepsi Opener” (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - “Percussion Score”; “Willis Rapp”; “Chartis Specialist” (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - “Philly Will Song” (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - “P.H.S. Alma Mater” (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - “Pitt Victory Song” (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Playing the Recorder (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - “P.M. Magazine” (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - “P.M. Magazine II” (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - “Pomp and Circumstance” (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - “Pregame Fanfare”, September 1960 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - “Power of Gold” (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - “Prelude C# Minor”, November 1962 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - “Prelude No. 2”, November 1962 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - “Puff of Smoke”, February 27, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - “Purdue Cheers” (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - “Purdue Hymn”, October 12, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - “Purdue Promo” (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - “Purdue Spirit”; (Rag) (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - “Put Your Hand in the Hand” (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - R-Book; Vocal Copies Masters (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - “Raging Bull”; (Cavelleria Rusticana) (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - “Rah Rah for Spartans”, December 6, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - “Reach Out” (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - “Reach Out II” (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - “Rebel Battle Cry”, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - “Red Cedar March”; Brass (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - “Remember Pearl Harbor” (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - “Reverse Fight Song No. 1 and No. 2”, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - “Reverse Fight Song”, November 3, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - “Reverse Hall”, October 1981 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - “Revelli Fanfare” (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - “Rhode Island” (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - “Ritual Fire Dance” (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - “Road Runner Theme” (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - “Rock Around the Clock” (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - “Rocket America” (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - “Rock A Bye Your Baby” (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - “Rock A Bye Your Baby”; with a Dixie Melody, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - “Round and Round”, February 16, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - “Round and Round II”, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - “Rubberband Man”, October 29, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - “Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer” (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - “Russian National Anthem” (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - “Russian Sailor’s Dance” (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - “Rutgers” (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - “Sabre Dance”; B-S-2 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - “Sabre Dance II” (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - “Saints in Concert”, October 1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - “San Antonio Rose” (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - “San Francisco Fanfare”, May 23, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - “San Jose”, November 5, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - “Santa Claus is Coming to Town” (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - “Santa Claus Wants A Tuba for Christmas” (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - “Saturday in the Park” (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - “Saturday Night”, January 7, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - “Say it With Music”, November, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - “Schlitz” (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - “See the U.S.A. in Your Chevrolet” (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - “Senior Salute”, November 17, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - “September”, February 15, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - “Service Medley”, November 11, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - “Shadrack” (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - “Shaft” (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - “Shangri-La” (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Shanty”; (“In Old Shanty Town”); Marching-B Vocal (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sheet Music (with hand written notes) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Show No. 4, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - “Should Do It” (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - “Show Biz Chasers and Tags” (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - “Silly Love Songs” (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - “Silverado” (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - “Silver Threads” (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - “Sinfonia Fanfare", February 14, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - “Sing, Sing, Sing” (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - “Sing U.C.L.A.”, September 1, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - “Skater’s Waltz” (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - “Sky High” (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - “Slaughter on Tenth Avenue”, September 1963 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - “Slippery Rock Fight Song”, October 1, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - “Something for Cat”, July 1963 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - “Son of a Preacher Man” (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - “Song of India” (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - “Soulful Strut” (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - “The Sound of Music” (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - “Soundpower”, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - “Soundpower”, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - “South” (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - “South Carolina” (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - “South Dakota” (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - “South Rampart Street Parade” (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - “Spartan Drums”, October 18, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - “Spartan Showcase” (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - “Spirit of Miami University”; University of Miami, September 13, 198 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - “Sports Network Incorporated Theme” (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - “Spotlight Intros” (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - “St. Elmo’s Fire” (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - “St. Louis Blues”; M-5-7 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - “Stand Up” (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - “Stand Up and Cheer” (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - “Stand Up, Stand Up” (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - “Stan Kenton” (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - “Star Spangled Banner”, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - “Star Spangled Banner Fanfare” (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - “Star Spangled Banner Fanfare”, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - “Stars and Stripes Trio” (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - “Stardust”, February 25, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - “Stereo Fanfare” (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - “Stow High School Alma Mater”, July 18, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - “Stranger In Paradise” (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - “Strauss Odyssey”, September 2, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - “Strauss Odyssey II” (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - “String of Pearls” (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - “The Stripper” (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - “Stereo Fanfare A and B” (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - “Stereo Festival Fanfare” (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - “Stereo T.R.P. Fanfare”, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - “Sunkist Fanfare” (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - “Sunny”, September 24, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - “Sunshine Tribute” (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - “Superstar” (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - “Supersuds” (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - “Swanee River”; “Old Folks at Home” (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - “Swanee”, September 1962 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - “Sweet Georgia Brown”, September 8, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - “Sweet Georgia Brown II”, October 21, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - “Sweet Georgia Brown III”, October 2, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - “Sweet Sue”, September 1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - “Sweetheart”; No. 6 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - “Tailgate Ramble”, July 1963 (Box 22, Folder 5)